[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "You can use FTP to download a video file.  It stands for this.", "correct_answer": "File Transfer Protocol", "incorrect_answers": ["File To Person", "Fast Transfer Protocol", "Full Transfer Protocol"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many players typically play a hand of classic Mahjong?", "correct_answer": "4", "incorrect_answers": ["8", "6", "3"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the scientific name for an aardvark?", "correct_answer": "Orycteropus afer", "incorrect_answers": ["Troglodytes pan", "Loxodonta aficanus", "Muscous domesticus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This sharks white belly and grey back make it difficult for prey to spot.", "correct_answer": "great white shark", "incorrect_answers": ["hammerhead shark", "tiger shark", "whale shark"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Of all the gliding animals, which one is the one best glider?", "correct_answer": "Flying lemurs", "incorrect_answers": ["Sifaka", "All of these", "Flying squirrels"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many Academy Awards did the 1990 movie Dances with Wolves win out of twelve nominations?", "correct_answer": "Seven", "incorrect_answers": ["None", "Twelve", "Five"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "All mammalian amino acids have which Greek letter designating their relation to the carbon atom to which different groups are attached?", "correct_answer": "Alpha", "incorrect_answers": ["Delta", "Sigma", "Beta"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The lack of this vitamin may cause seborrhea and dry skin.", "correct_answer": "Vitamin B6", "incorrect_answers": ["Vitamin J", "Vitamin D", "Vitamin F"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What O-word can be added to each of the following to make a new meaningful word:\nWit, Board, Field", "correct_answer": "Out", "incorrect_answers": ["Old", "Oaf", "Oat"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What geographic area did the guinea pig originate from?", "correct_answer": "South America", "incorrect_answers": ["Africa", "Australia and New Guinea", "North America"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The domino effect, a term named after the domino game, denotes what peculiar sequence of events?", "correct_answer": "Consecutive events triggering one another", "incorrect_answers": ["Simultaneous events caused by a small event", "A series of unexpected events", "One big event causing a series of simultaneous small events"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who plays Rosie in the movie Princess Protection Program?", "correct_answer": "Demi Lovato", "incorrect_answers": ["Vanessa Hudgens", "Miley Cyrus", "Selena Gomez"]}]